I never would have imagined this.
To be able to see the moon
from Yoshiwara...
Oh, don't be so silly.
You came to Yoshiwara only after
its liberation. Isn't that right, sir?
No...
It existed long ago...
The ceiling may have been shut,
but the moon existed back then.
A small, brave, and beautiful moon.
Again?
The seventh one this month.
We can no longer ignore this.
At this rate, Yoshiwara...
will never be able to recover.
Also...
Thank you for your patronage, sir.
Of course.
I see.
Thank you very much!
Excuse me.
No, excuse me.
You've come a long way,
Tsukuyo.
Give up on being a woman,
If you wish to become one who protects
instead of one who is protected,
give up on being a woman.
You may not be the sun which
shines above the people.
But I, alone, know of your beauty which
secretly illuminates the land.
I, alone, shall watch over you.
I, alone...
will protect you.
Ma-
(新八)あの～ 銀さん｡
(銀時)どうしたよ？ 新八｡
一応 聞いておこうと
思ったんですけど➡
先週の予告で発表したｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝって
いったい何すか？
Whatcha doing, Tsukuyo?
また あれですか？ いつもの…｡
Gin-san and everybody are here!
終わる終わるｻｷﾞ？ 違うって！
Wake up already!
I'm gonna leave without ya!
今日はﾎﾝﾄに ｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝやるから｡
銀さん 大人だから➡
I'm coming.
さすがに そんなに
ｳｿばっかついてられないから｡
Go on ahead.
Don't forget to spruce yourself up.
信用に関わってくるからね｡
(神楽)まだ この番組に
信用なんてあると思ったｱﾙか？
ひどい 神楽ちゃん！
もう どこで覚えてきたの？
そんな言葉！
だって しかたないですよ銀さん｡
最終章突入って言ったの
去年の今頃ですよ｡
もうこれ １年も最終章
やっちゃってることになりますよ｡
それに ３年目のﾗｽﾄの
ﾆｾ最終回の騒ぎもあったし｡
あぁ あれな｡ いや～ あれは➡
最終回ｺﾝﾄが
やりたかっただけで➡
騙すつもりはなかったんだけどね｡
Spruce up, is it?
["It's Bad Luck to See a Spider at Night"]
さすがにもう みんな
この番組のやり方に➡
耐性ついてるかな～って
思ってたんだけど｡
番組開始直後から ﾃﾚﾋﾞ東京に
問い合わせの電話多数ね｡
Hey, it's been a while.
Sheesh, still looking as dull as ever.
しかも ﾎﾞｸが
｢ｻﾝﾗｲｽﾞがあんなことに…｣➡
なんて言ったもんだから
ﾈｯﾄの検索ﾜｰﾄﾞで➡
And you still look as much like
a burnt field as ever.
ｻﾝﾗｲｽﾞがﾄｯﾌﾟになる始末ですよ｡
Hey! What's that supposed to mean?!
あの時の台本 最初は➡
｢ｻﾝﾗｲｽﾞが倒産しました｣
だったからね｡
You'd better not be talking about my hair!
そりゃ当時のﾌﾟﾛﾃﾞｭｰｻｰ
偉い人に呼び出されて➡
Come on, it's been a while
since we last met.
Could you two please stop fighting?
｢株式会社を何だと思ってんの？｣
って怒られるわ｡
Now that everyone's here,
we can have a blast!
たまたま放送観てた
ｽﾀｯﾌの実家からも➡
Sorry, Seita.
｢ｱﾝﾀ 『銀魂』終わるみたいだけど
仕事は次 大丈夫なの？｣って➡
Huh?
Could you wait outside for a moment?
What?!
Hold on!
ｵﾝｴｱ中に電話が来るし
身内まで騙して どうするね！
I haven't even been in
a close-up shot yet!
That's all the screen time I get?!
はいはい わかった わかった！
反省してます！
You should be glad that everyone
was able to see you so happy.
だから今日は
ﾎﾝﾄにｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝやるから｡
No way!
絶対 ｳｿつかない｡
ﾎﾝﾄですか～？
You've crossed the line here, Mom.
ﾎﾝﾄに ｱﾆﾒ 『銀魂』ｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝ ｱﾙか？
ﾎﾝﾄだって！
This is what I get, after
waiting half a year?
You see, what I wanted to talk
to you guys about...
Screw them.
この銀さんの目を見て｡
ｳｿついてる目に見える？
Stupid show.
I even sat back from the TV in a well-lit
room every week to watch this show.
いや… ＢＧｵﾝﾘｰなんで
よくわからないです｡
Hey, now. Give me a break.
そんなわけで ｱﾆﾒ 『銀魂』ｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝ
このあとすぐ！
ごまかした!?
I didn't come here to work today.
Pretty please? Savior of Yoshiwara?
There is certainly more freedom in
Yoshiwara after Hosen's death.
However, we have some new vermin who used
to stay clear of Yoshiwara because of Hosen.
After all, there was nothing more powerful
than Hosen to deter crime.
To be honest, the crime rate was
lower with Hosen around.
There's no end to the assaults,
burglaries, break-ins,
and other crimes committed by
the Anti-Foreigner Faction.
The members of the Hyakka
aren't able to keep up.
The biggest problem in Yoshiwara
at the moment
would be the sale of illegal drugs.
Prostitutes whose bodies and
souls have been worn out
turn to drugs for a moment of pleasure.
This town may appear at peace,
but they've already spread far
and wide in the shadows.
There's one man running most
of the business in Yoshiwara.
Fujinosuke Hashiba, said to be
Yoshiwara's best customer...
No, his name holds no meaning.
He has many names.
Not only names.
He has multiple titles and faces.
ﾜｰｵ！ ｢ｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝ銀魂｣を
ご覧のみなさん こんばんは！
But I doubt that any are
grounded in reality.
今回は たくさんのご投票
ありがとうございました｡
それでは
さっそく いってみましょう｡
He must be laughing as we struggle
to find incriminating evidence,
『銀魂』名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞ 注目の１位は？
while he buys Yoshiwara women, drinks liquor,
(３人)ﾀﾞｳﾝ！
ｶｳﾝﾄ！
and watches as this town
collapses around him.
How are we supposed to
catch a guy like that?
坂田銀時 ｷｻﾏは亡霊でござる｡
I barely deserve the title
of Yoshiwara's Savior.
かつて 侍の国を護ろうと
晋助らとともに戦った思い｡
You should know.
それを捨てられず
妄執し とらわれ➡
I'm doing business under the table here.
生きた亡霊だ！
Nevertheless, we need your
familiarity with this world.
おぬしの護るべきものなど
もうありはしない！
亡霊は
帰るべきところへ帰れ!!
Don't worry.
I have a lead.
What?
I saw a spider.
ﾚｸｲｴﾑを
くれてやるでござる｡
While I was on watch, I clearly saw it.
A spider tattoo on that man's neck...
あっ 弦が！
おい にいちゃん｡
A spider, huh?
ﾍｯﾄﾞﾎﾝ取れ ｺﾉﾔﾛｰ！
Not much to go by, but oh well.
I'll have to let myself be caught.
いつの間に拙者の弦が…｡
何してる!? 撃て！
In the spider web.
C'mon! Place your bets!
耳の穴かっぽじって
よ～く聞け！
Evens or odds?
Make your choice!
ｵﾚは 安い国なんぞのために
戦ったことは➡
Place your bets!
Even!
Odd!
一度たりともねえ！
Even!
They all have spider tattoos?
国が滅ぼうが侍が滅ぼうが
どうでもいいんだよ！
The Benigumoto (Red Spiders).
ｵﾚは昔から…｡
This gambling parlor is on their turf.
There wouldn't be any problem if they
spent all their time rolling dice,
but they're the ones claiming to be
Anti-Foreigner Faction as they
rob, threaten, and kill people.
A bunch of thieves willing to do anything.
Well, I wouldn't say that they're cut out to take
over as the big evil group in Yoshiwara,
はい そんなわけで➡
『銀魂』名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞ１位は
坂田銀時さんで➡
but there may be a connection.
｢今も昔も俺の護るもんは
何一つ変わっちゃいねｪｪ!!｣➡
You should get going.
I'll stand out if I have a woman with me.
でした｡ いや～ さすがｵﾚだわ｡
Besides, women can't stand
many-legged creatures.
やっぱ すげえな
｢ｼﾞｬﾝﾌﾟ｣ｱﾆﾒの主人公は｡
ﾏｼﾝｶﾞﾝの弾も避けて通るわ…｡
Fool.
って ちょっと待て～!!
ちょっ… これ➡
How could the leader of the Hyakka
run away at this point?
本当に ただの
『ｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝＴＶ』じゃねえか！
Besides, I've already said that I stopped
being a woman long ago.
そうだよ｡ 銀さん ｳｿつかない！
You're the type that's guaranteed
to press charges
いや ｳｿじゃないけど
これ十分 ｻｷﾞだよね？
if my elbow happens to poke
your boob on a packed train.
(神楽)つい ﾉﾘで一緒に
｢ﾀﾞｳﾝ！｣って叫んでしまったｱﾙ｡
Leave, stupid.
Then go ahead and touch me.
つ～か 今日
もしかして 毎年恒例の➡
I don't mind.
Huh?
秋のｸｰﾙ替わりの総集編ｱﾙか？
ｲｸﾞｻﾞｸﾄﾘｨｰ！
I won't let myself be taken lightly.
Touch me.
やぁ 毎年 上半期の予算を➡
I'm not going to touch you.
I don't want any unnecessary trouble.
この時期には
すっかり使い果たしてるから➡
You won't run into any To Love-Ru.
[Note: To Love-Ru, a sexy-romantic-comedy that was published in JUMP. It's pronounced the same as "trouble".]
１本 総集編を
やってるんだけどさ｡
Fool.
いや なまなましい話は
やめてください｡
Just touch me already.
Hey, don't underestimate To Love-Ru.
今年は 少～しだけ
予算が浮いたから➡
Wake up to find a naked girl in your bed.
こうして
ＣＧが作れちゃったわけだよ｡
Trip and dive into another girl's crotch.
まぁ あんだけ迂回ﾙｰﾄの
おまけを重ねてくれば当然ね｡
Even your little sister doesn't mind.
I told you, stuff like that won't happen!
Touch me already!
そうそう
このｱﾆﾒ 『銀魂』４年目自体が➡
Cut it out!
今までの３年間についてきた
おまけみたいなもんだからね｡
A girl shouldn't say stuff like that!
You're supposed to save that
phrase for when it counts...
ひどいこと言うな！
じゃあ 仕切り直して➡
名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞの続きの紹介いくか！
A spider!
つ～か このﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞ いったい
いつ投票 受け付けてたｱﾙか？
ちゃんとやってたじゃん
｢ｼﾞｬﾝﾌﾟ｣のほうで｡
いつの話だよ それ！
(３人)ﾀﾞｳﾝ！
ｶｳﾝﾄ！
Huh?
This is...
Wh-What...
What do you think you're doing?!
ﾊﾞｶ野郎！
なんでも 一人で
しょいこみやがって｡
Hey...
憎まれ役まで 一人で
請け負うつもりか！
This isn't how you said it'd be?
Zip it.
ｵﾚは 知ってるんだぞ ﾄｼ｡
You have no right to talk.
Uh...
お前が ﾐﾂﾊﾞとの…｡
Who are you people?
残念です｡
ﾐﾂﾊﾞも悲しむでしょう｡
Which gang y'all from?
古い友人を
なくすことになるとは｡
あなたたちとは➡
Why ya peekin' in our place?
仲よくやって
いきたかったのですよ｡
'Fess up.
I was getting some puff-puff action.
新撰組の後ろ盾を
得られれば➡
Like hell you were!
Come up with a better lie!
自由に商いが
できるというもの｡
Uh, that's actually what I was doing.
そのために縁者に近づき➡
More like, I was forced into doing it.
縁談まで
設けたというのに➡
Don't insinuate anything weird.
In any case, we were just doing
some puff-puff action.
まさか あのような
病持ちとは…｡
Nothing suspicious about us at all.
You'd be pretty damn suspicious if that
was what you were actually doing!
端から ｵﾚたち
抱き込むために➡
ｱｲﾂを利用するつもり
だったのかよ｡
Uh, to be honest...
愛していましたよ｡
We're a couple of thugs who wanna
join the Benigumoto.
商人は 利を生むものを
愛でるものです｡
Wha-?!
What? Thugs?
ただし 道具としてですが｡
Heh, you've got balls.
You brought a woman to come
see me, the great Unkai,
head of the Benigumoto?
せめてよ 死ぬ前に
いっときでも➡
No way.
I never meant to offend you.
Cut me some slack, Unkie Turd.
人並みの幸せ 味わわせて
やりてえんですよ｡
Who are you calling Unkie Turd?!
I've just been a little constipated lately.
We're a married thug couple.
外道とは言わねえよ｡
Huh?!
ｵﾚも似たようなもんだ｡
Both of us are intent on joining
the Benigumoto together.
ひでえこと
腐るほどやってきた｡
Right? We're a couple of thugs.
あげく
死にかけてるときに➡
Wha...?!
We had our kids grow mullets.
その旦那
叩き斬ろうってんだ｡
ひでえ話だ…｡
And we force them to
wear tattoo jackets.
同じ穴のﾑｼﾞﾅ
というﾔﾂですかな｡
That's right.
鬼の副長とは
よく言ったものです｡
I lead a gang of girls.
あなたとは
気が合いそうだ｡
Gintoki was top dog at West High.
I was attracted to his lone wolf attitude
and got knocked up and married at 17.
そんな
たいそうなﾓﾝじゃねえよ｡
Rode the winds of Shonan during pregnancy
and ended up with twins.
Dia and Block have hair
down to their waist now.
[Note: The names combine to form "Diablock",
a Japanese block toy similar to Lego.]
ｵﾚは ただ…｡
Dia? Block?
You gave your kids some crazy names!
いや～ さすが土方さん！
Boss!
締めるところは締めますね！
かっこいいな！
No doubt about it!
These guys are genuine thugs!
って… あれ 銀さん？
Why not let them join?
なんか納得がいってない顔
してますけど｡
I'd be more than happy
to welcome this babe.
当たりめえだろ！
なんで ｱｲﾂが２位なんだよ！
Even if she's damaged goods.
ｱｲﾂ かっこつけてるけど➡
Come on, she's married.
もう 今や
ただのﾎﾞｹｷｬﾗの一人じゃん｡
Exactly.
そうｱﾙ！ ﾏﾖﾗｰで ﾄｯｼｰね｡
急に ｼﾘｱｽなｾﾘﾌ言われても➡
I get turned on when I take something
that belongs to another person.
Let's ice the husband and take turns
getting some of that puff-puff action!
全然説得力ないｱﾙ｡
なぁ～！
いや ｱﾝﾀらに
言われたくないよね 土方さんも｡
Don't take me lightly.
だいたい ｱｲﾂの名ｾﾞﾘﾌっていやぁ
こんな感じだろ？
I could skewer every single
one of you in an instant,
if I wanted to.
And here's a heads-up.
My husband is a hundred
times stronger than me.
(２人)ｲﾋﾋﾋﾋ！
ｱﾝﾀら ﾎﾝﾄ ひどいことしますね！
Your husband's been skewered.
なんつ～ 悪意ある編集
するんですか！
Wha-?
じゃあ すっきりしたところで
名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞの続きを➡
You threw it without any warning.
Say something next time.
(３人)ﾀﾞｳﾝ！
ｶｳﾝﾄ！
Sorry.
The husband aside, this woman
should prove useful.
It can never hurt to have
too many bodyguards.
ﾊｧ ﾊｧ ﾊｧ…｡
Work your asses off.
Gintoki. What if, what if...
these Benigumoto have absolutely
nothing to do with the case?
What will happen to us?
Yeah, well... you know?
We'd be treated as accomplices,
and that's the end of that.
What do you mean, the end of that?
Don't you mean the end of us?
Huh? What do we do then?
Go pole vaulting? In Hawaii or something?
Hey, do you want to die?
Besides, where is this car even headed?
これまでか…➡
Don't worry about it.
敵の手にかかるより➡
It's probably going to a drug warehouse.
We'll find a link there.
最後は 武士らしく➡
Uh, excuse me.
潔く 腹を切ろう｡
Where are we going?
A kamaboko plant.
[Note: Kamaboko = processed fish meat]
ﾊﾞｶ言ってんじゃねえよ｡
A kamaboko plant, he said.
Isn't that nice?
立て｡
I happened to be hungry.
No, it's not!
What exactly did you come here for?
And what kind of business do they
have with a kamaboko plant?
Must be, y'know?
Some kind of new drug that's
made from kamaboko?
We're going to run over the plan
before we reach the site.
あれ？ なんか 今の
ｾﾘﾌは聞いたことあるんですけど➡
Grab as much kamaboko
as you can and run for it!
画は ﾃﾚﾋﾞで観たことない感じ｡
ﾂﾞﾗも 銀ちゃんも
なんか ｸｫﾘﾃｨｰ上がってるｱﾙ｡
What plan?!
These people just want
to steal kamaboko!
気にしない 気にしない｡
去年のｱﾆﾒﾂｱｰの映像が
混ざってても 気にしない｡
Okay, we're here!
The kamaboko team gets off here!
おい～！ いいの!? それ！
The illegal drug team should remain seated
until we reach the warehouse.
権利関係とは 大人の事情が
いっぱいあるんですよ！
大丈夫｡ 今ごろ ﾌﾟﾛﾃﾞｭｰｻｰが➡
Illegal drug team and kamaboko team?
関係各所に ｽｰﾂ着て
調整して回ってるから｡
What kind of selection is that?
全然 大丈夫じゃねえよ それ！
Hey, get off!
じゃあ 気になるﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞの続きは
ＣＭのあと！
You're on the kamaboko team!
Grab as much kamaboko
as you can and run for it!
ﾀﾞﾗﾀﾞﾗ続くね｡
Excuse me, I can't stand kamaboko,
so please put me on the drug team.
♪♪～
The sight of that pink layer
makes me want to hurl.
｢ｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝ銀魂｣を
ご覧の皆さん こんにちは｡
Oh really...
Then I'll grab sasa-kamaboko for you.
[Note: Sasa-kamaboko = white
leaf-shaped kamaboko]
高橋瞳と｡
(みんな)BEAT CRUSADERSです！
Why are you joining in
the kamaboko raid?!
はい ということで 今回は
ｵﾚたちのね…｡
We managed to get on the drug team.
ﾎﾝﾄ １位とったって感じで➡
ﾎﾝﾄ ありがとう｡ じゃあ最後
それでは 聴いてください｡
Hey, why is the kamaboko
team arming up?
(みんな)『ｳｫｰｱｲﾆｰ』！
Are they planning on risking
their lives for kamaboko?
♪♪～
Hey, what about the drug team...?
Gintoki, are we going to be okay?
Probably.
No, I'm pretty sure we aren't okay.
We're fine.
It's getting hard to do business
around here.
We aren't getting any drugs to sell.
They're all going to Yoshiwara.
The drug business has
moved underground.
Lowly thugs like us can't do any business without the
permission of the organizations who run the place.
There's been a change up top.
No, I suppose that the top
was forcibly changed.
In the past, there were constant turf wars
between the various gangs around.
But now, our leaders have all been killed,
so we have to hold hands
and do business
for the same man.
There are this many spider tattoos on
people besides the Benigumoto...
It appears that thieves and Faction members
have been gathered from all over.
The gang we're in is like the company
you'd outsource your grunt work to.
I suppose so.
高橋瞳さんと
BEAT CRUSADERSの皆さん➡
What could a bunch of kamaboko
thieves be good for?
ありがとうございました｡
って この番組
もう どこがｱﾆﾒなのか➡
However...
わけわかんないんですけど｡
We've found a lead.
いいや！ ｢銀ﾀﾏｲｷｰ｣まで
やったｵﾚたちに➡
The one single lead that will take us
もう 境界線はねえんだよ！
to the nest of the boss spider.
言われりゃ そうですよね｡
Who is that man?
では 引き続き
『銀魂』名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞ➡
今度は ４位から６位までを
一気に紹介➡
No idea.
The top leaders don't even
know his identity.
ｶｳﾝﾄ～ ﾀﾞｳﾝ！
Different people know him by different
faces and different names.
All we know is that he's crushed
a number of groups by himself.
人間にしては よくやった｡
Using some kind of phantasmagoric
technique...
ﾌﾝ｡
ﾌﾌﾌ…➡
And his monstrous power...
おい ﾃﾞｶﾌﾞﾂ｡
He used that power to set up a web
on this side in the blink of an eye.
ﾃﾒｴら 終わったな｡
Playing detective is fine,
but you oughta be careful.
完全に
春雨を敵に回したぞ｡
今に 宇宙中に散らばる
春雨が➡
That man's web is vast and deep.
ﾃﾒｴらを殺しに来るだろう｡
Step on even one of his threads
知るかよ｡
終わんのは ﾃﾒｴだ｡
and you'll become entangled
いいか？ ﾃﾒｴらが 宇宙のどこで
何しようと かまわねえ｡
and eaten.
Leaving no remains behind.
だが…｡
Shoot! We've been spotted!
理解できねえか？
今どき弔い合戦｡
Hey, you've gotta be kidding me!
しかも
人斬りのためにだぜ｡
Out of all that crowd,
and from that location?!
He wasn't a common criminal after all.
わかってんだよ｡ んなこたぁ｡
His sharp detection skill
and his kunai weapon.
A ninja?
No, his skills are more like a...
って いいかげんにしろ ｺﾗ！
この天ﾊﾟｰ！
ど ど どうしたの 神楽ちゃん？
お前さっき あのﾏﾖﾗｰのこと
さんざん文句言っといて➡
Damn! We're completely surrounded!
ﾌﾀを開ければ 自分はﾏｼﾞﾒなこと
ばっかり言ってんじゃねえか！
お前 そんなんでいいｱﾙか？
『銀魂』のﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞが➡
Baby spiders crawling all over the place.
ﾏｼﾞﾒなｾﾘﾌで埋め尽くされて
平気ｱﾙか？
This is why I hate spiders!
そ そんなこと言ったって
ｵﾚが選んだﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞじゃないし｡
『銀魂』観てくれてるみんなの
公正な意見というか… なぁ新八｡
Gintoki, I'll buy us some time!
You return to Yoshiwara and notify
Hinowa and the Hyakka about this!
いや 神楽ちゃんの
言うとおりだよね｡
ﾎﾞｸも納得できないな｡ つ～か
ﾎﾞｸのｾﾘﾌ出てきそうにないし｡
Don't be joking!
You think I'll leave a girl behind
in a nest full of sleazy men?!
ｺﾗｯ ﾀﾞﾒｶﾞﾈ！ ﾃﾒｴ 裏切んじゃねえ！
こんな感じに修正すれば
『銀魂』っぽくなるよ｡
I'm the one staying!
じゃあ もっかい４位から６位
ｶｳﾝﾄ ﾀﾞｳﾝ｡
I'm the one who brought
you into this mess.
Go, quickly!
I'll follow behind shortly.
Sorry, but I try not to take a woman's
last minute nonsense seriously.
Stop treating me as a woman.
I've already told you, I've stopped being
a woman along with these scars.
Ha! For someone who screams
over a puff-puff action,
you sure talk big!
Please go, I beg you.
ﾋｬｰﾊｯﾊｯ｡
おい ｵﾚのいいｾﾘﾌ➡
ｱﾊﾊｯ｡
I wish to stay as your equal.
あんなところに
ﾋﾟｰｯてかけたら ｵﾚ➡
完全になんか卑猥なこと言ってる
ようにしか聞こえねえじゃん！
When I'm with you, my resolve weakens.
そのほうが銀ちゃんらしいね｡
Give up on being a woman,
んなわけねえだろ｡
この …どもが｡
Tsukuyo.
いやぁ そういうｾﾘﾌや画に
修正が入るのも➡
Don't shake up my feelings any further.
『銀魂』ならではですよね｡
うるせえ ｶﾞﾝﾊﾞﾘｽﾄ！
誰が ｶﾞﾝﾊﾞﾘｽﾄだ！
では ７位 ８位の発表と
今までの修正 ﾓｻﾞｲｸ総集編を➡
Pay attention, you idiot!
お通ちゃんの曲にのせて どうぞ！
You're the one
who's not paying attention.
ここで立ち止まったら→
♪♪～
[Preview]
How can you be alive?!
Who the hell are you?!
You don't have a chance against him.
The Original Head of the Hyakka...
I alone will protect you.
寺門通ちゃん
ありがとうございました｡
["Once You're Entangled in a Spiderweb,
It's Hard to Get It Off."]
Master?!
名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞも
残すところ あと２つ｡
Boys and girls across the country,
GinTama Gymnastics are starting!
９位と10位だけね｡
そういえば なんでｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝなのに
１位から発表してるｱﾙか？
No, they aren't.
普通 逆じゃないの？
Can you stop trying to jump
on every bandwagon?
いやぁ たまんねえだろ｡
この企画の尻すぼみ感が｡
Oh, yeah? No good?
後先考えてねえ感じが｡
No good.
[The real Pirameki Gymnastics are up next,
on the TV show PIRAMEKINO!!]
あっ
もう言い訳する気もないんだ｡
ほんじゃ 第９位は 例のあれです｡
心ゆくまで聞いてください｡
[Pirapirapi~ra! Pirapi~ra~!]
(３人)ﾀﾞｳﾝ｡
ｶｳﾝﾄ…｡
[See you next week.]
逃げるぞ 銀時！
ﾂﾞﾗか… ﾂﾞﾗ ｺﾀﾛｳか!?
行くぜ… ﾂﾞﾗ｡
なぁ ﾂﾞﾗ？
なんだ ﾂﾞﾗか…｡
って しつこいわ！ あの人
何回 名乗れば気が済むんですか！
もう途中から 言葉の意味が
よくわからなくなってきたね｡
ｹﾞﾘしてから後悔ｱﾙ｡
それ ｹﾞｼｭﾀﾙﾄ崩壊の間違いだよね｡
まぁ これで あとは10位のみだ｡
いったい誰のｾﾘﾌが
ﾗｽﾄを飾るｱﾙか？
いや～ 楽しみですね！
10位ってところに
ﾎﾞｸもかすかな希望を感じます｡
じゃあ
名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞ 最後の１つ！
(３人)ｶｳﾝﾄ ﾀﾞｳﾝ！
何だよ母ちゃん…
今日は日曜だぜ｡
ったく
ｵｯﾁｮｺﾁｮｲなんだから｡
今日は火曜だ！
ﾃﾒｴ！ こうしてる間に攘夷浪士が
乗り込んできたらどうすんだ!?
仕事なめんなよ こら！
ｵﾚが いつ仕事
なめたっていうんです？
(３人)って またお前か～い！
ﾌﾌﾌ やっぱりね こういう企画は
余が出んことには締まらんからな｡
ﾃﾒｴ！ この前
高杉にｵﾒｴが声当てたとき➡
どんだけﾌｧﾝから
苦情がきたと思ってんだ！
２通？
んなわけねえんだよ！
まずいですよ 銀さん！
今度はよりによって沖田さんを…｡
新八… 私
なんか お腹痛くなってきたね｡
ｹﾞﾘしてから後悔ある｡
あっ！
ちょっと待って 神楽ちゃん!!
新八 あとは任せた｡
え？ おい！ ちょっと待っ…｡
これ どう締めればいいんですか？
まかせておけ 苦しゅうないぞ｡
では 余がおさらいする｡
銀魂 名ｾﾞﾘﾌﾗﾝｷﾝｸﾞ ｶｳﾝﾄﾀﾞｳﾝ！
え～っ！
♪♪｢ﾃｨﾝﾄﾝｼｬﾝたら ﾃｨﾝﾄﾝﾁﾝ｣
♪♪｢あ ｿﾚｿﾚ｣
ひでえな これ…｡